prolificliving.com 2017-10-01

# Privacy Policy

**Prolific Living Inc. respects your privacy.**  
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Prolific Living. In addition, we capture web server logs that have your IP address, type of browser and other kinds of technical information that honestly we never look at unless there is a major problem!

Bottom line: If you entrust your name and email to us, we promise to only send you the information that you wanted to receive!

**Cookies**  
A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows you to be recognized you each time you visit this site. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Prolific Living Inc. does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be collected by some of the services used on this website like Facebook Like Buttons, Twitter Tweet buttons, etc.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Google Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Information on how to opt-out of other third-party vendor’s use of cookies can be found by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**External Sites**  
Prolific Living Inc. is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information to them.  

This privacy policy was last updated on: February 3rd, 2013  
If you have any additional questions about this policy, please [contact Prolific Living](https://www.prolificliving.com/contact-prolific-living/)
